到目前为止，在本系列讲座中，我们假设存在图像。我们拍了一张照片
So far in this lecture series, we've assumed the presence of an image. We've taken an image
从文件。我们从连接到电脑的相机拍摄了一张照片。我们抓住了一个
from a file. We've taken an image from a camera attached to our computer. We've grabbed an
来自互联网的图像。现在是时候谈谈图像是如何形成的。
image from the Internet. It's time now to talk about how images are actually formed.
图像在相机内形成，它们实际上形成在背面的视网膜上
Images are formed within cameras and they are actually formed on the retina at the back
我们的眼睛。有一个非常迷人的图像形成方面，我们采取三维
of our eye. There's a really fascinating aspect of image formation, we take the three dimensional
我们生活的世界，这对我们来说非常真实，我们将它投射到两个方面。
world that we live in, that's very real to us and we project it into two dimensions.
因此，当我们有一个图像，一张照片或类似的东西时，它是平的，它是唯一的
So when we have an image, a photograph or something like that, it's flat, it's only
二维的。所以我们采取了三维的东西，并将其转化为二维的东西。
two-dimensional. So we've taken three-dimensional things and transformed it into two-dimensional things.
我们只有三个维度，所以我们扔掉了一个，现在我们有两个。
We only had three dimensions to start with, so we've thrown away one, now we've got two.
必须有一些后果。有一些非常有趣的后果
There's got to be some consequence of that. There are some very interesting consequences
尝试将三个维度压缩成两个。
of trying to crunch three dimensions down into two.
但这还有另一个非常有趣的方面。那就是我看一张照片
But there's another really interesting aspect of this. And that is if I look at a photograph
虽然我知道它是扁平的，但对于我来说它看起来是三维的
of a landscape, it looks three dimensional to me, even though I know it's flat, it's
一张照片，我可以用手抚摸它，它是完全平坦的。所以有一些魔力
a photograph, I can run my hand over it, it is perfectly flat. So there's some magic going
在我的脑海里，我正在重建那些实际上并不存在的维度
on in my head, where I'm reconstructing dimensions that don't actually exist and that just comes
从我个人对世界三维性质的体验;我的脑子
from my own personal experience of the three dimensional nature of the world; my brain
填补这个额外的维度。
fills in this extra dimension.
所以这些是我想在这组中谈论的图像形成的方面
So these are the aspects of image formation that I want to talk about in this group of
三个讲座。在本讲座中，我们将了解如何使用针孔形成图像
three lectures. In this lecture we're going to look out how images are formed using pinhole
带镜头的相机和相机以及本讲座中的处理都是几何的;
cameras and cameras with lenses and the treatment in this lecture is all going to be geometric;
这是关于类似的三角形。我们还将看一些不同类型的相机;
it's about similar triangles. We're also going to look at a few different types of cameras;
我们将看看鱼眼摄像机和全景摄像机以及一种非常新型的摄像机
we're going to look at fisheye cameras and panoramic cameras and a very new type of camera
称为“光场相机”。
called a "Light Field Camera".